### INFO:



# **Dmytro Hoi**Python Developer

E-mail: <a href="me@dmytrohoi.com">me@dmytrohoi.com</a>
LinkedIn: <a href="dmytrohoi">dmytrohoi</a>
Telegram: <a href="mailto:@dmytrohoi">@dmytrohoi</a>

Site: <a href="hoid.dev">hoid.dev</a>

### SUMMARY:

I've been programming in Python for almost 4 years. I worked on the following major tasks: the creation of a quality control system for the Big Data/ML project (Python and JS); creating and maintaining a custom Python test framework based on Appium for a medical embedded project (complex medical device on Android); creation of bots for Telegram, Slack and Discord (Python, JS); creation of site parsing scripts (Python, JS, complex Regex); creation of Bash/zsh console scripts for personal projects (e.g. site deploying, environment setup); contribution to open-source projects on GitHub (e.g. python-telegram-bot, aiogram); creation of plugins and a plugin loader for a game (Minecraft, Java, Jython); creation of a personal site (Fastify, ReactJS, Cloudflare Workers). I also teach Python and Basic Development courses at a famous IT school, create a company-wide bot to automate hiring proccess, and write articles on well-known resources.

I finished studying Systems Analysis, including machine learning.

## SKILLS:

- Languages: Python, JavaScript, Ruby, bash scripting, Go (learning in progress).
- Libraries/Frameworks: FastAPI, ReactJS, Django, Flask, pytest, appium, jest, python-telegram-bot/aiogram, SQLAlchemy/Gino, requests, Tkinter
- English-level: Intermediate (good reading and listening, but poor speaking skills)
- Tools: Git, SVN, adb, cron, Docker, venv/pipenv/poetry
- Other: zsh, Regex, GitHub (with Actions), sr.ht
   Details on my site: hoid.dev

## ADDITIONALS SKILLS:

- Initiative, automation integration, and proactive
- Public speaking and teaching skills
- Writing articles (<u>habr.hoid.dev</u> | <u>devto.hoid.dev</u> | <u>dou.hoid.dev</u> | <u>blog.hoid.dev</u>)
- Also: SMM, PR, Poems writing, musician

### WORK EXPERIENCE:

Company: Grid Dynamics

**Position:** Python Software Developer (09/2021 - now)

Info: Implementation of a tool to run tests in multiple languages from Python with an API

server, and additional tool (stack: fastapi, django, reactjs)

Company: Grid Dynamics

**Position:** Automation QA Engineer (02/2021 - 09/2021)

**Info:** Creation Quality Control system for Big Data/ML project (stack: flask, reactjs)

Company: GlobalLogic

**Position:** Automation QA Engineer (05/2019 - 02/2021)

Info: Implementation of a custom test framework for the embedded device on Android

(stack: Python, Appium, ADB, and pytest)

Company: Microbilt

Position: Site Scraping Script Developer (07/2018 - 05/2019)

Info: Programming with Regex and SQL. Python and Javascript automation scripting.

Company: National University of Radioelectronics

**Position:** Senior Assistant at Quality Assurance Department (06/2016 - 05/2017) **Info:** Creation and maintenance of an internal quality assurance system (ISO:9001).

### EDUCATION:



## Kharkiv National University of Radioelectronics

- Bachelor (2014 - 2018) Electronics - "Electronics devices and systems"

Master (2018 - 2019)
 System Analysis - "Consolidated information"

## PERSONAL PROJECTS:

- <u>hi gain dev</u> personal programming blog
- freelancehunt-api a framework for public API on Python (PyPI)
- <u>afilters.is</u> advanced filters for JS (<u>NPM</u>, <u>docs</u>)
- pyplugins plugin loader for the famous game on Java and Jython (Minecraft)
- <u>pelican-gsb</u> a tool for quickly building Pelican-based websites on Python (<u>PvPI</u>)
- slack-bolt-router slack-bolt request routing tool (PyPI)
- other projects: bots (e.g. <u>nurecraft-bot</u>), scripts, and programs with a GUI My personal projects are collected in <u>hoid.dev/#projects</u>.

DMYTRO HOI / Jan 2022 2/2

E-mail: <a href="me@dmytrohoi.com">me@dmytrohoi.com</a> | LinkedIn: <a href="dmytrohoi">dmytrohoi</a> | Site: <a href="hoid.dev">hoid.dev</a>